[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "Would you mind telling me _____ boy joined the soccer team?",
        "answer": "which"
    },
    { "question": "Do you think _____?", "answer": "we have enough time to eat" },
    {
        "question": "Could you tell me _____.",
        "answer": "if Ken has gone to America"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you think _____ she paid full price for her bag?",
        "answer": "X"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you have any idea _____?",
        "answer": "where Ray goes to school"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you think _____ ABC Company has a good business model?",
        "answer": "X"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you remember _____ the students need to participate in this activity?",
        "answer": "if"
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you tell me _____ they like about this particular restaurant?",
        "answer": "what"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you have any idea _____ they baked the cookies themselves?",
        "answer": "if"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you remember _____ they bought their car?",
        "answer": "where"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you remember _____?",
        "answer": "if she has taken the course"
    },
    { "question": "Do you know _____ the meeting room is?", "answer": "where" },
    {
        "question": "Could you tell me _____?",
        "answer": "when our English Class is"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you have any idea _____ brought us the chocolate?",
        "answer": "who"
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you tell me _____ I could borrow this computer for a while?",
        "answer": "if"
    },
    { "question": "Do you know _____?", "answer": "what this word means" }
]